<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<NamespaceComments Namespace="JinxBot.Controls" Assembly="JinxBot.Controls">
    <summary>
        <para>The <b>JinxBot.Controls</b> namespace contains classes to efficiently build rich user interfaces centered around chat 
        uses.  Classes such as the <see>DisplayBox</see> and <see>ChatBox</see> enable design-time support for these controls within
        your project, and coupled with easy-to-understand utility classes such as the <see>ChatNode</see>, building a rich user interface
        should take minimal time.
    </para>
        <para>Additionally, the JinxBot chat displays are extensible by creating new <see cref="ChatNodeRenderer">ChatNode renderer classes</see>.  
        By implementing the logic of chat node rendering into a separate class, the rendering can be decoupled from the display box itself, enabling 
        users to create custom chat node displays.  This is achieved through the <see>ChatNodeRendererAttribute</see>, which should be applied 
        to the custom ChatNode-derived class.
    </para>
        <para>The JinxBot.Controls project is licensed under the terms of the modified BSD license as specified in the 
        <a href="http://www.jinxbot.net/controls/license.txt" target="_blank">accompanying license.txt file</a>, with the following additional terms:
        <list type="bullet">
            <item>
                <description>Contains derivative software based on the ShinyDesign project, which is licensed under the modified
                terms of the BSD license located <a href="http://www.robpaveza.net/shinydesign/license.txt" target="_blank">here</a>.
                </description>
            </item>
            <item>
                <description>Contains derivative software based on the DockPanel Suite v2.2 by Weifen Luo, which is licensed under
                the following terms:
            <pre><![CDATA[
The MIT License

Copyright (c) 2007 Weifen Luo (email: weifenluo@yahoo.com)

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
]]>
            </pre>
            </description>
            </item>
        </list>
    </para>
    </summary>
</NamespaceComments>